http://www.mbgc.com.sg/privacy-policy/

Play.
Marina Bay Golf Course
Marina Bay Putting Course
Practice Greens
Driving Range
View.
Facilities
Gallery
Book.
FAQ
Read.
Contact Us
Play.
Marina Bay Golf Course
Marina Bay Putting Course
Practice Greens
Driving Range
View.
Facilities
Gallery
Book.
FAQ
Read.
Contact Us
Book.
Golf Course
Putting Course
Book.
View available tee times and make a booking.
Check Availability
View Golf Charges
Book.
Enjoy 6 holes of fun and challenges on our putting course.
View Charges
Home / Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy describes the practices in which Marina Bay Golf Course, my golf kaki and NCI Golf Pte Ltd collect, use and disclose Personal Data collected from you.
For the purpose of this Policy, “Personal Data” shall mean data, whether true or not, about an individual which can be identified – from that data; or from that data and other information which an organisation has or is likely to have access. Such Personal Data shall also refer to the data which is already in our possession or the data to be collected by us.
It supplements but does not supersede nor replace any other consent that you may have previously provided to us, nor does it affect any right that we may have at law in connection with the collection, use, disclosure and / or retention of your Personal Data.
1          Personal Data Collected
1.1       We may collect your Personal Data in various situations such as account / member sign-up, newsletter subscription, golf game booking, event photography and participation in lucky draw / survey / event / activity, etc.
1.2       Personal Data collected by us may include name, NRIC/FIN/Passport number, email  or postal address, contact number, date of birth, nationality, bank account / credit or debit card details, photographs and images, particulars of your home club if any, and information of the products or services you may have purchased from us.
1.3       Where Personal Data of any third party are provided by you to us, you undertake to obtain the consent of the third party to our collection, use and/or disclosure of those Personal Data in accordance with our Privacy policy. We reserve the right to request for the verification of such consent where required.
2          Use of Your Personal Data
2.1       By interacting with us and submitting information to us, or signing up for any products or services offered by us, you agree and consent to us for collecting, using, and disclosing such Personal Data in the manner set forth in our Privacy policy.
2.2       We may collect and use your Personal Data for the following purposes:
- To provide the products and / or services you have purchased;
- To assist you with your enquiries;
- To process payments for your purchases;
- To improve customer service;
- To conduct statistical analysis and research including building analytical solutions;
- To keep you updated of our future offers / promotions and events; and
- To comply with applicable laws and regulations
3          Updating You on Our Offers / Promotions
3.1       You may be contacted via email, text message or voice call, to be informed of our latest offers or promotions.
3.2       You may also receive non-marketing messages such as surveys, customer service notices and other service related notices if you have signed up as a member under any of our membership schemes or utilised any of our services / facilities.
4          Disclosure of Your Personal Data
4.1       We may disclose your Personal Data to the following organisations for the purposes mentioned above:
- NTUC and entities in the NTUC Group;
- NTUC Club and its subsidiaries;
- Financial institutions including credit card companies and their service providers;
- Business partners;
- Agents, contractors, data intermediaries or third party service providers;
- Hospitals, clinics or insurance companies in connection with claims;
- Professional advisor such as legal advisers, auditors; and
- Regulators or other government bodies as required by law.
5          Use of Cookies
5.1       We may use cookies on our websites to record session information, collect visit and access details to our web pages that enable us to continue to improve our services and provide better and useful features to our website users.
5.2     Should you wish to disable the cookies associated with these technologies you may do so by changing the settings on your browser. However, please note that this may affect the functionality of the website(s).
5.3       We are not responsible for the Personal Data policies (including Personal Data protection and cookies), content or security of any third party websites linked to our websites.
6          Protection of Your Personal Data
6.1       We maintain appropriate security safeguards and practices to protect your Personal Data from accidental loss, misuse or destruction, in accordance with the applicable laws.
7          Accuracy of Your Personal Data
7.1       We take all reasonable and practicable measures to ensure that your Personal Data remains accurate, complete and up-to-date. Please keep us informed when there are any changes to your Personal Data. As a my golf kaki member, you have declared and are responsible to furnish accurate personal data and to maintain the accuracy of your personal data which is provided to my golf kaki on their membership website.
8          Access and Correction of your Personal Data
8.1      You may request access to or make corrections to your Personal Data records, subject to some exceptions allowed by law. A fee may be charged to cover the cost of providing the requested information and we will respond to your request within 30 days.
8.2       Please submit your request to us at the following email addresses:
Marina Bay Golf Course  :  dpo@mbgc.com.sg
my golf kaki                      :  dpo@mygolfkaki.com
9          Storage and Retention of Personal Data
9.1       We will delete, as reasonably possible, or otherwise anonymise any Personal Data in the event that the Personal Data is not required for any reasonable business or legal purposes, according to our data retention policies.
9.2       We may from time to time transfer your Personal Data overseas to server owned by third party service providers, for storage purposes and to continue to provide our services to you.
9.3       Where your Personal Data is transferred in this manner, we will ensure that the recipient of the Personal Data is bound by legally enforceable obligations to provide to the Personal Data a standard of protection that is at least comparable to that under the Personal Data Protection Act 2012.
10        Minors
10.1    We cannot distinguish the age of persons accessing our websites. If a minor (according to applicable laws) has provided us with Personal Data without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should contact us to inform us and we shall restrict any collection, use or disclosure of that personal data.
11        Contacting Us
11.1    If you have any questions about our Personal Data protection policy or practices, or wish to withdraw your consent to any use or disclosure of any Personal Data provided to us, you can write to Marina Bay Golf Course at dpo@mbgc.com.sg or my golf kaki at dpo@mygolfkaki.com.
12        Policy Updates
12.1    We may update our Privacy Policy at any time in response to changes to applicable laws or our practices. You are advised to check our Privacy Policy on this page regularly.
13        Governing Law
13.1    This Policy is governed by and shall be construed in accordance with the laws of Singapore.
Last Updated 29 August 2019
Advertisement
Awards.
Home.
Play.
Marina Bay Golf Course
Marina Bay Putting Course
Practice Greens
Driving Range
Probably the Best Public Golf Course in Asia.
View.
Book.
Read.
Be Informed.
I accept the terms & conditions.
Connect with us
Marina Bay Golf Course
80 Rhu Cross, Singapore 437437
+65 6345 7788
Probably the Best Public Golf Course in Asia.
Copyright © 2018 Marina Bay Golf Course. All Rights Reserved.
Play.
Marina Bay Golf Course
Marina Bay Putting Course
Practice Greens
Driving Range
View.
Book.
Read.
This site uses cookies, by continuing to browse the site you are agreeing to our use of cookies. Find out more.
